本字幕由 YYeTs人人影视 原创翻译制作
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新 请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
■
翻译：装汁的容器    Soomii    红豆包    Iz
校对：Ｊ小糯      时间轴：grace
■
后期：鱼骨头      总监：stephanie
《开心汉堡店》
第一季第七集
我回来啦
I'm back.
这是什么
What's all this?
我们打算在放周末长假时把房间都租出去
We're renting out rooms in our apartment for the long weekend.
周末长假:  节假日与周六周日连起来
形成三四天小假期
我们准备办个简易旅馆
We're gonna be a Bed and Breakfast.
Bed and Breakfast:  只提供早餐的小旅馆
一般是普通民宅开办的
我好兴奋哦
It's so exciting.
我超爱简易旅馆
I love Bed and Breakfast.
-又古典又新奇  -是么
- They're so quaint. - Aren't they?
随便叫几个陌生人来
Random strangers
弄得满屋子都是皮屑很爽么
shedding skin cells all over the house.
我反对举办简易旅馆
Ugh, I'm against this Bed and Breakfast
虽然我很反感
as much as you can be against something,
但我不会出手阻挠
and still, let it happen.
这就好比每当我前妻
Like when my ex-wife wanted to
想跟我们的邻居  雷  玩3P的时候
have a three-way with our neighbour, Ray.
泰迪  泰迪
Teddy, Teddy.
我认为现在谈论这个话题很不...
I don't think you should be talking about...
等等  你们和那个
Wait, you had a three-way with Ray,
-在码头边卖东西的雷玩3P吗  -没错
- the guy who wears the sales suit down on the pier? - Yeah.
可是我没跟他们一起玩
I mean I wasn't involved,
我只旁观  不过  是3P没错
I just watched. But... yeah.
昨天上自然课的时候  我也玩了回3P
I had a three-way in science class yesterday.
苔米的实验搭档没来上课
Tammy's lab partner was absent
所以她加入到我和乔伊这组
so she joined in with me and Joey.
-那堂课很有趣  -好了  到此为止
- It was fun. - Okay, enough.
油油  盐盐
Oilies, salties,
超级贵的卫生纸
extra-expensive toilet paper...
我喜欢软的东西
I love that soft stuff.
举办简易旅馆就是为了赚点补贴
I thought we were doing this to make extra money.
赚点钱都让你败在这些东西上了么
Isn't all this eating into our profits?
别担心  鲍勃
Don't worry, Bob.
钞票会有的  口碑也会有的
It's gonna be money and online reviews,
等我死后升入天堂  上帝会对我说
and when I die and I go to heaven, God's gonna say,
你就是那位开办简易旅馆的女士吧
"Hey, aren you the lady who rented the B&B
我有所耳闻
I heard about?"
然后我会说  我的主  是这样的
And I'm gonna say, "Yes, God..."
-您想来点什么  -来  拿着
- "What can I get you?" - Here, hold this.
闻闻
Mm, smell.
来  闻闻嘛
Come on, smell it.
你都插到我的鼻孔里了
You're shoving things in my nose.
来闻闻这个
Smell this one now.
你总是这样  琳
You always do this, Lin.
当你想找乐子时  总是玩得太过火
Whenever you entertain, you put way too much effort into it
还把自己搞得疯疯癫癫的
and drive yourself crazy.
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?
-我是超完美房东  -不  琳达
- I'm a wonderful hostess. - No, Linda.
你总是过于热情
You go overboard
如果大家表现得不够感激  你就发飙
and then if people aren't appreciative enough, you snap.
一派胡言
That's not true.
我有做房东的天赋
I'm a gifted hostess
现在我准备向专业房东迈进
and I'm ready to go pro.
-真柔软  -请把它卷回到纸筒上
- It is really soft. - Put it back on the roll, please.
老妈  为啥不直接把蒂娜放在厕所边上呢
But, mom, what if we just put Tina by the toilet?
-好耶  -我不介意
- Yeah. - I don't mind.
欢迎光临简易旅馆
永远的好朋友
登记时间快到了
Almost check-in time.
蒂娜  吉恩  你们的房间收拾好了吗
Tina, Gene, are your rooms guest-ready?
-好了  -我感觉好了
- Yeah. - Subjective.
还记得你俩嘲笑我搬到衣柜住那茬吗
Remember when you made fun of me for moving into a closet?
现在你们两个傻逼得腾出房间  我就不用
Well now you suckers have to give up your room and I don't.
来客人了
A guest!
扎维  是一位昆虫学家
Javee... is an entomologist.
-扎维德  -什么
- Javed. - What?
我叫扎维德
My name is Javed.
好吧
Alright.
昆虫学家是什么科的医生来的
What kind of doctor is an entomologist again?
腺科  股科
Glands, butt?
我不是股科医生啦
Ha, I'm not a butt doctor.
我是研究昆虫的
I study insects,
专门研究真菌甲虫的交配习惯
specifically the mating habit of the my fungal beetle.
什么风把你吹到我们这里来了
Oh. So what brings you here?
真菌甲虫以真菌为食
My fungal beetles feed on fungus,
这座城市的真菌繁殖力非常非常旺盛
and this town has a very, very high potency of fungus.
那正是我们市的口号
Uh, that's actually our town motto.
真菌市
Fungus town!
蒂娜  你带扎歪歪歪德
Tina, why don't you show Javeeed...
-扎维德  -去他的房间看看
- Javed. - his room...
-扎歪德  -扎维德
- Jav-ed? - Javed.
你要入住的是马术套房
You'll be in the equestrian suite! Huh?
好的
Okay.
好极了  他把甲虫装进罐子带到我们屋里
That's great. He brought a bug in a jar into our house.
别搞种族歧视
Don't be racist!
这间屋子是我亲自装扮的
I decorated it myself.
你
You...
非常  喜欢  马呀
like horses a lot.
你很喜欢罐子
You like jars.
这些是标本罐
Oh, these are specimen jars.
我想让虫后与雄性甲虫交配
I intend to mate the queen with a male
然后把她的卵保存起来
and preserve her eggs.
你是说  你要看着这些甲虫互相交配吗
You mean you're gonna watch beetles have sex with each other?
酷
Cool.
那是干嘛的
What's that for?
这是人工合成的信息素
Ooh, this is a synthetic pheromone.
它和虫后为吸引雄性甲虫
It's similar to what the queen emits
而分泌的化学物质相类似
when she wants to attract males.
喷在人类身上管用吗
Does it work on human boys?
不管用
Oh, no.
也许管用
Well, maybe.
我能把这些放在厕所里吗
May I store these in the bathroom?
没问题  大家都会喜欢的
Sure. Everyone would love that.
又有客人来了
More guests!
欢迎光临
Welcome!
你们一定是埃德和诺拉
You must be Ed and Nora Samuels!
-是的 你好 -你好
- Yes. Hello. - Hi.
来 快进来
Come on, come in.
我带你们看看房间
I'll give you the tour.
这里是客厅
Okay, this is the salon.
一会儿我们要在这里举行欢迎会
This is where we're gonna have the meet-and-greet,
你们来得正是时候
and you're just in time!
其实呢  我们只想去自己的房间待着
Actually, we'd just like to go to our room,
可以吗
if that's okay?
对  我们只想安顿下来
Right. We'd just like to get settled.
什么  为什么
What? Why?
待在这里参加欢迎会嘛
Stay here for the meet-and-greet.
我们可以过一会儿再出来
Maybe we'll come back out in a bit.
不要嘛  待在这里嘛
No, stay.
会很有趣的哦
It's gonna be fun.
蒂娜  把扎维德叫来
Tina, get Javed!
我想他正在睡觉
I think he's napping.
叫醒他
Wake him up!
让我们荡起双腿
So, let's go around
一起玩个小游戏
and we'll, um, we'll play a little game.
说一说自己最尴尬的时刻
Let's say what our most embarrassing moment was.
谁想说说
Who wants to go?
那我说了
I'll go.
一次我在吃圣餐时咳嗽了几下
One time I coughed at communion,
结果圣饼正好从我的嘴巴飞出去
and the wafer flew right out of my mouth
掉在我的胸上
and it landed on my boob!
谁想下一个说  扎维德
Who wants to go next? Javed?
我还是算了吧
I'll take a pass.
我想听听下一位的故事
Get me on the next one.
老爸烫卷发那段怎么样
What about when dad got a perm?
那不是卷发  是波浪发
It wasn't a perm, it was a body wave.
美国著名女演员  女歌手  全能艺人
在各个领域都有杰出贡献
你当时看上去就像
You looked like
《压轴赛》里的芭芭拉・史翠珊
Barbra Streisand in "The Main Event".
-你的发型看起来就像她的阴毛  -确实
-You looked like Barbra Streisand's pubes. -I did.
老爸在墨西哥餐厅用西语说谢谢那段呢
How about how dad says gracias in Mexican restaurants?
那段太了
That's embarrassing.
记得那次  你让我给你检查前列腺
Remember the time you asked me to check your prostate
结果你拉出一坨屎
and you made a poopie?
琳达
Linda!
记得老爸想去慢跑那次吗
Oh, remember when dad tried to go jogging?
有完没完
Oh, come on!
还记得老爸在《心的方向》剧终时
What about when dad cried
大哭特哭那次吗
at the end of "About Schmidt"?
吉恩  你怎么只穿了条内裤
Gene, why are you in your underwear?
我刚才在吃饭
I was eating.
怎么  你想让我的衣服都蹭上黄油吗
What, you want me to get butter all over my clothes?
要是蹭上了  我们就把他拖出去
Yeah. Now we just take him out back
用水龙带给他冲一冲
and hose him off.
你是医生吧  这个是痣吗
You're a doctor.  Is this a mole?
我不是医生  还有  那个是葡萄干
I'm not a doctor. And that's a raisin.
可以吃的痣
Oh... edible mole.
好了  让我们听听其他人的段子
All right, let's let someone else go.
塞缪尔夫妇  你们呢
Samuels, how about you,
你们最尴尬的时刻是什么时候
what's your most embarrassing moment?
我不知道
I don't know.
-现在吧  -没错  就是现在
- This? - Yeah, definitely this.
行了吗
Are we done?
行了  诺拉
Yes, I guess we are done, Nora.
你确定这附近没有别的地方可以住吗
Are you sure there aren't any rooms available anywhere else?
没有  别的旅馆都住满了  我查过
No, everything's booked... I checked.
房东  你好
Ooh, hello.
我有点冷
I'm cold.
我的乳头全都挺起来了
My nipples are so pointy!
叮咚  有人找你
Ding-dong! It's for you.
有可能是包裹哦  你应该来应下门
It might be a package... You should answer it.
琳  别烦了  快睡吧
Lin, stop stewing and go to sleep.
我能不烦嘛  鲍勃
I can't help it, Bob!
我们的客人大煞风景
Our guests are such party poopers.
真扫兴  一点都热闹不起来
All of them! No one has any B&B spirit at all!
好了  快睡觉吧  好吗
Okay, just go to sleep, all right?
明早起来就好了
You'll feel better in the morning.
好吧
Fine!
吉恩  吉恩
Gene, gene,
你的脚贴在我屁股上干嘛
your foot is down the back of my underwear.
那里暖和  我脚丫子冷
It's warm down there, my feet are cold.
但那里是我的屁股啊
Yes, but it's my ass.
老爸  你还没睡吗
Dad, are you still awake?
是的  蒂娜
Yes, Tina.
刚才我还在和吉恩讲话来着
I was just talking to Gene, right?
一眨眼的功夫吧
A second ago?
马儿是不是脑中有歌唱不出
Do you think horses get songs stuck in their heads?
苍天啊  我不知道
Oh, my God. I don't know.
蒂娜  快睡觉
Tina, go to sleep.
老爸  想来点鸡肉吗
Dad, do you want any chicken?
别跟别人说哦  我拿的只够我们俩吃
Don't tell anyone, there's just enough for the two of us.
都给我睡觉  你们几个
Just go to sleep, all of you.
客人们睡得安稳  我很欣慰  琳达
I'm glad our guests are comfortable, Linda,
挤在一张床上可"舒服"死了
'cause this is great!
我们的客人
Oh! Our guests!
会感谢我的
They'll appreciate me.
下次我会加倍努力
I'll just have to try harder next time.
你干嘛
Hey!
我还有一只
I've got a backup.
我干活的兴致头一次这么高涨
I've never been so happy to be at work.
你们店今天开得很早嘛  鲍勃
Yeah, you opened early today, huh, Bob?
这儿有一条直通楼上浴室的管道
Well, there was a line to get into the bathroom up in the apartment,
所以我在楼下洗碗池边  刷刷牙洗洗脸
so I came down here to do my morning routine in the slop sink.
鲍勃  楼下有牙签吗
Bob, do we have any toothpicks down here?
在那边
Yeah, over there.
有好看的牙签吗
Pretty ones?
"好看的牙签"是什么意思  琳
What do you mean, pretty ones, Lin?
好看呗
The nice ones.
琳达  旅馆办得怎么样
How's the B&B going, Linda?
好极了  怎么  你听到什么风言风语了
Oh, it's great! Why? What'd you hear?
没什么  我敢打赌楼上一定妙如仙境
What? Nothing. I bet it's magical up there.
我的脑中是一派英格兰风情
I picture it like England.
没错  泰迪  是这样的
It is, Teddy, it is.
可他们欣赏吗
But do they appreciate it?
他们像脏兮兮的小地鼠一样躲在房里不出来
Holed up in their rooms like dirty little gophers?
如果不出来热闹热闹
Why come to a B&B
那来住简易旅馆还有什么意思呢
if you're not gonna participate, you know?
这些不领情的家伙
Oh, they're so ungrateful!
我要是能住在你的简易旅馆里就好了
I wish I was staying at your B&B.
我会坐在客厅里
I'd sit in the parlor,
品品酒
and maybe I'd have a little wine,
下下棋
play some board games...
耶  品酒  下棋
Yes! Wine! Games!
泰迪  你应该住在这里
Teddy, you should stay here.
什么
What?
没错  你就是我的梦中客人
You should. You're the dream guest
-真的吗  -你就是那个我一直在找的人
- Really? - You're the one I'm looking for.
你们还有房间可以住吗
Do you have any vacancies?
有  露易丝的房间
Yes! Louise's room!
等一等  琳达  露易丝的房间
Whoa, whoa, whoa, Linda, Louise's room?
她会杀了我们的
She'd murder us.
她是大姑娘了  她会挺过去的
She's a big girl... She'll get over it.
琳达  她不会的
Linda, she won't get over it...
你去打扫她的房间
When you vacuumed in there,
她会一整个礼拜都不跟你说话
she wouldn't talk to you for a week.
还有  那根本不是房间  只能算个壁橱
Plus, it's not even a room, it's, like, a closet.
听起来正适合我  我不需要太多空间
That sounds perfect for me... I don't need a lot of room.
我只带一套衣服就够了
I'll just bring, like, one outfit.
太好了  我去把我的东西拿过来
Oh, I love it! I'll get my stuff.
好棒好棒哦
This is gonna be great!
享受一下你告诉露易丝这事儿时
Well, have fun telling Louise
她那强大幽深的怨念吧  琳
you're kicking her out of her room, Lin.
戴个头盔吧
Wear a helmet.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
你好啊  露易丝  我只是...
Oh, hi, Louise. I was just...
你好啊  老妈
Oh, hi, mom.
-你好  -你抱着我的东西
- Hello. - You're holding my stuff.
你好  我的大小姐
Hello, my little lady.
你好  老妈
Hello, mom.
你拿我东西干什么
What are you doing with my stuff?
我只是欢迎一下新房客入住你的房间
I was just welcoming our newest bed-and-breakfast guest into your room.
我的房间
Into my room?
跟泰迪打声招呼
Say hello to Teddy!
你好  露易丝
Hi, Louise.
你房间里的东西都好好玩哦
You got wonderful stuff in here.
我超  超  超爱它
I love, love, love it!
什么
What?
除了这个小家伙  它让我有点怕怕
Except for this little guy, he's kind of giving me the creeps.
不是吧
This isn't happening!
母亲大人  这不是真的  对不对
Mother, this isn't happening, right?
这个世界疯了吗
Has the world gone crazy?!
行了行了  露易丝
Okay, come on, Louise.
让我们的客人清静一会儿
Let's leave our guest alone.
你是说你的客人吧
You mean your guest,
我可没让他乱进我的房间
'cause I did not invite Teddy to come into my room
乱动我的东西
and move my stuff around!
好了好了
That's right.
走吧
Come on.
等会芝士酒宴上见  泰迪
See you in a little bit at the wine-and-cheese mixer, Teddy.
听起来不错  琳达
Sounds good, Linda.
咱们地狱见  泰迪
And I'll see you in hell, Teddy.
非常抱歉  泰迪
I'm sorry, Teddy.
咱们撒旦面前评理去
I will see you in hell!
塞缪尔夫妇去哪了
Where are the Samuels?
芝士都快化了
The cheese is getting sweaty.
他们在自己房里
They're in their room.
我猜他们正在床上蹦Q呢
I think they're jumping on the bed.
我听见床垫里的弹簧响个不停
I heard the box spring going crazy.
他们听起来很"忙活"嘛
Sounds like they're "busy".
他们应该忙着品尝奶酪和美酒吧
They should be busy eating cheese and sipping wine.
你说他们忙是什么意思
What do you mean, "they're busy"?
他们也有作业要做吗
Like, they got homework?
不  他们...   那个...
No. They're... it's...
忙着蹦Q  他们就不能休息一下吗
Busy jumping, they can't take a jumping break?
扎歪  你回来啦
Ah, Javay! You came back
来点美酒和芝士吧
for the wine and cheese!
别错过美酒佳肴哦  干  干  干
You got to catch up. Chug! Chug! Chug!
快看这些雄甲虫
Whoa, look at all those males.
没错  蒂娜
Yes, Tina!
这些幸运的雄甲虫里会有一只跟虫后交配
One of these lucky bugs will mate with the queen,
之后虫后会咬掉他的头
and then she will bite off his head.
好浪漫哦
So romantic.
来点芝士吧
Cheese?
不要  谢了
No, thank you.
吃啊
Eat it.
吃点嘛
Aw, have some.
张嘴  张嘴
Open your mouth. Open the mouth.
尝一下嘛
Just try it.
你会喜欢的
You're gonna love it.
真的好好吃哦
It's really good.
吉恩  你怎么吃了那么多
Gene, you're over your limit!
我...
Well, I...
虽然很想品尝一下美酒和芝士
hate to miss wine and cheese,
但是这些小家伙们相亲的时间到了
but it's time for these little fellas to meet their mates.
再见
Bye-bye.
等等  我也想看
Wait. I want to watch.
我跟你说  琳达
Well, I'll tell you, Linda,
我正享受着我的美丽人生
I'm having the time of my life.
你再也不会听到我有半句怨言
You're not gonna hear me whining about it.
whine:  名词意为"酒"
动词意为"抱怨"
你好  美酒
Hey, "Whine."
你们真应该来听听这个段子
Everyone should be here for this!
真不知道你们错过了多妙的一个段子
They don't know what they're missing!
我在  走廊里  听到  这个笑话
I heard the joke from the hallway.
-露易丝  你喜欢吗  -喜欢
- Do you like that, Louise? - Yeah.
真是  真是太好笑了
Oh, it was... was really funny!
滚出我的房间
Get out of my room.
我是这里的房客
I'm your guest in your room.
你和你妈妈谈过了吗
Did you talk to your mommy?
那间屋子不是我妈的  是我的
It's not my mommy's room, it's my room.
是  我知道  我已经付了75块钱
No, I know, and I paid $75,
我只在你屋里住几个晚上就走
and I'm just going to stay in your room for a couple of nights.
露易丝  来点芝士吧
Louise, put some cheese in your mouth.
好吃吧
Mmm, isn't that delicious?
是啊  很容易下咽
Yeah, it really goes down easy,
是不是啊  泰迪
doesn't it, Teddy?
你听好了  泰迪
Just so you know, Teddy,
限你一个小时滚出这里
you have one hour,
要不我就动真格的了
then I get real.
一小时后  扎维德的房间
如果我是信息素  会在哪里放着呢
If I were a pheromone, where would I be?
泰迪的房间
晚安  扎维
Good night, Javee!
晚安
Oh! Uh.. Good night.
疯子
Crazy lady.
她是个疯子  是吧
She's a nut. Am I right?
你们好坏哦
Oh, you're bad!
晚安  泰迪
Good night, Teddy!
晚安  琳达
Good night, Linda!
-睡个好觉  -做个好梦  琳
- Sleep tight! - Sleep tighter, Lin.
别让臭虫咬了哦
Don't let the bed bugs bite!
不会的
I won't.
我的枕头有股怪味
Hey, my pillow smells funny.
晚安  塞缪尔夫妇
Good night, Samuels!
对不起  对不起
Oh, woo! I'm sorry! I'm sorry.
-上帝啊  -上帝啊
- Oh, my God! - Oh, God!
把门关上好吗
Could you please close the door?
-上帝啊  -好  抱歉  抱歉
- Yeah. Oh, my God. - Okay. Sorry. Sorry.
-不  你还在门外  -好了  好了
- No. With you on the other side of it. - Okay. All right. All right.
滚开
Leave!
塞缪尔先生为什么戴着手铐
Why is Mr. Samuels wearing handcuffs?
他们...
They are...
他们是逃脱大师
They are escape artists.
真的吗
They are?!
真的  很有趣吧
Yes. Isn't that interesting?
行了  该睡觉了  我们走
Okay, time for bed. Let's go.
露易丝  因为你是新来的  不懂规矩
All right, Louise, since you're new here,
我就发发慈悲告诉你各地盘范畴
I'll show you the ropes.
床那边是餐饮区
That corner of the bed is for eating.
这边是活动区
This right here is the exercise area.
这里是鱼跃区
This is where I thrash.
好吧  我站着  谢你们十八辈祖宗
Yeah. I'll stand, thank you very much.
开始行动
Here we go.
你和你妈妈谈过了吗
"Have you talked to your mommy?"
你怎么不和你妈谈谈  泰迪
Why don't you talk to your mommy, Teddy?
谈谈你的新室友
About your new roommates.
大家都去哪了
Where is everybody?
小心点  鲍勃  我掺了点昨天剩的芝士
Careful, Bob. I reused the cheese from yesterday.
牙签我都没摘  直接煎蛋饼里了
Some of the omelettes have toothpicks in them.
早上好  扎维
Oh, good morning, Javee!
你和你的小虫子们都饿了吧
I hope you and your bugs are hungry.
我的几个标本瓶子不见了
My appetite is gone,
我的胃口也随之而去
along with several of my specimen jars.
精强力壮的雄甲虫都在那些罐子里呢
They contained my most virile males.
不是吧
Oh, no.
挥着翅膀的虫虫
Ah, little insects with wings.
他们能飞多远呢
How far could they go?
大家好
Hey, guys.
怎么了  我的头发被压走形了吗
What? Do I have bed head?
天啊  泰迪
Oh, good God, Teddy.
我的甲克虫
My beetles!
怎么了
What?
泰迪  你的脸上全是甲壳虫
Teddy, you've got beetles all over your face.
是吗  我还没照镜子呢
Is that right? I haven't looked in the mirror yet.
这些雄甲虫正处于发情旺盛期
These males are in an extremely amorous state.
你是说  他们此刻正在跟泰迪的脸交配吗
You mean, right now they're trying to mate with Teddy's face?
是的
Yes.
天啊  小泰
Oh, God, Ted.
-疼吗  -不  不疼  别担心
- Does it hurt? - Nope. Nope. Don't worry about it.
泰迪  你应该去医院看看
Teddy, you should probably get to the hospital.
你还能开车吗
You okay to drive?
不  我不用去医院  没事的
No, I don't need a hospital. I'll be fine.
这个周末仍然很愉快
This is still a magical weekend.
你知道吗
You know?
他真是个超完美房客
He's the perfect guest.
-早餐吃什么  -鸡蛋
- What's for breakfast? - Eggs!
什么都治不了这个家伙
Ugh! Nothing gets to this guy.
你  我不知道你是怎么弄的
You! I don't know how,
但这绝对是你干的了
but you did this.
我知道她是怎么弄的
I know how she did it.
她往他脸上喷了信息素
She used my pheromones on him.
好了  琳达  大家伙
Okay, well, uh, Linda, everyone,
过家家玩得开心点
have fun in the B&B.
我要到楼下餐馆工作了  再见
I'll be downstairs in the restaurant. Bye.
再见  老爸
Bye, dad.
别走  你得管管她啊
No! You deal with her!
她简直无法无天了
She's out of control!
好吧  把她的房间还给她
Okay. Uh, give her her room back.
-不行  -我只会这一招
- No! - Well, that's all I got.
再见
Bye.
露易丝
Louise!
你被禁足了  滚回你的房间
You're grounded. Go to your room.
好极了  我巴不得呢
Gladly. That's all I ever wanted.
不  我指的是我的房间
No, I mean my room.
回我房间去
Go to my room.
你无权逼迫我
You can't make me.
我就有  娇蛮大小姐
Oh, yes, I can, Miss missy.
好吧  有就有
I guess you can.
我从没见过这些甲克发情发得这么厉害
I've never seen these beetles so aroused.
我挑起了它们的欲望
I have that affect on beetles.
我好久没做了
I haven't had this much action in a while.
他们明早还会来叫我吗
Are they gonna call me tomorrow?
也许不会吧  不过没关系
Probably not, right? That's okay.
泰迪  虫子爬你满身  你还能开玩笑
Teddy, making jokes, covered with bugs.
你是纯爷们  牛逼啊
You are a man! Damn you!
你有怕的东西吗
Does anything get to you?
别说  还真有
There's really only one thing.
-是什么  -穿着动物服的演员
- Yeah? - Costumed characters.
比如  在游乐场工作的那种
You know, like the ones in amusement parks.
-真的吗  -为什么
- Really? - Why?
因为他们的眼睛  吉恩
It's the eyes, Gene.
他们那冷漠  呆滞的眼睛
Their cold, dead eyes.
当他们干你老婆时  就用那双眼睛看你
Watching you while they make love to your wife.
-当他们干什么  -我是说
- While they what?! - I mean...
当他们  参加生日派对时
When they... uh... go to birthday parties.
好吧
All right.
谢谢你  泰迪
Thank you, Teddy.
谢谢你  母亲大人的钱包
Oh, thank you, mom's purse.
还要谢谢你  电话
Well, thank you, phone.
是的  我要打个电话
Yes, I will make a call.
我接住你了
Oh, I gotcha.
你在咝咝作响
Oh, you're sizzling.
我喜欢这声音
I love your sound.
你好  你们提供穿动物服的演员是吧
Oh, hello. You have costumed characters, right?
派对好友
太好了  我想要河马  狐狸
Oh, that's great. Ah, I'll take the hippo, the fox.
饼干  饼干
Here's a cookie. Here's a cookie.
饼干
And here's a cookie.
饼干来了
Brought you some cookies!
什么情况
What's going on here?
我们得回家了
Ah, we have to go home.
你们说什么呢
What are you talking about?
你们不能走  你们还在渡假呢
You can't leave. You're on vacation.
坐下
Sit down,
吃点饼干
enjoy the cookies,
穿上你的尖头胸罩
unpack your pointy bra
拿起你的鞭子抽打他
and your whip and whip him.
他是个坏小孩哦
He's a naughty boy.
-我是坏小孩  -上吧
- I'm a naughty boy. - Get to it!
你把门给锁上了吗
Did you just lock the door?
她把门给锁上了
She just locked the door.
我不知道你们在干嘛
I... I don't know what's going on.
到冰淇淋会餐的时候你们才可以出来
You can come out when it's time for the ice cream social!
你也是
You, too!
你好  超完美房客
Hey, there's my perfect guest.
你好  琳达
Hey, Linda.
我有个好消息
I got good news.
你将被升为
I'm upgrading you
白金会员
to platinum status!
Oh! Platinum status.
听起来很尊贵
That sounds fancy.
没错  你饿了吗
It is! You hungry?
你需要客房服务吗
You want some room service?
不饿  我想我还能吃点东西
No. Eh, I guess I can eat.
好  你想吃什么
Okay. What do you want?
培根汉堡
Uh... bacon burger?
-什么  -培根汉堡
- What? - Bacon burger.
-培根  -第一个词
- Bacon... - First word.
-培根  -一个字吗
- Bacon. - One syllable.
-不  是两个字  -两个字吗
- No. Two syllables. - Two syllables.
是...  猪
A... pig.
-恐龙  -培根
- Dinosaur. - Bacon!
-培根汉堡  -凯文・培根[美国演员]
- Bacon burger. - Kevin Bacon.
-第二个词呢  -汉堡
- Second word. - Burger.
刹车垫
Break pads?
恐龙
Dinosaur.
侏罗纪公园
Jurassic park!
哑谜
Charades!
你不能猜"哑谜"
You can't guess "charades".
我就猜这个
Yes, you can.
好吧  是哑谜吗
Oh. Is it charades?
母牛  汉堡  汉堡
Cow. Burger! Burger.
培根汉堡  猜对了
Bacon burger! All right.
好耶  培根汉堡
Yes. Bacon burger!
好的  这个可以有
All right. I can do that.
有人按铃  我去开
Uh, doorbell. I'll get it.
看你  "浑身是劲"
Oh, Footloose.
凯文・培根出演的电影
有什么事吗
Can I... can I help you?
这里有叫泰迪的吗
Is there a Teddy here?
泰迪  有人找你
Teddy, you've got visitors.
谢谢
Oh, thank you.
我们是毛茸茸人偶团  你是泰迪吗
We're the Fuzzy Buddies! Are you Teddy?
这是怎么回事
What's going on here?!
-别过来  -你看到我们很激动嘛
- No! - Someone's excited to see the fuzzy buddies.
-别  -搞什么
- Don't... - What?
你还挺有劲儿的
Whoa. You're a big bo... oh!
我的老天
Oh, my God!
泰迪
Teddy.
冰淇淋会餐要开始了
It's almost the ice cream social.
琳达  这到底是怎么回事
Linda, what is going on up here?
这里怎么一片狼藉
You're losing control of your B&B.
开什么玩笑
What are you talking about?
我们不是好好的吗
Everything is going perfectly.
对  对  琳  好你个头啊
Right. Right, Lin, everything's fine.
鲍勃  我的培根汉堡做好了吗
Bob, do you have my bacon burger?
对了  培根汉堡  这儿呢
Oh, yeah, the bacon burger. Here.
鲍勃  帮个忙好吗
Bob, can you help me?
我嚼不动
I can't chew.
-是要我喂你吗  -对
- You need me to feed you? - Yeah.
嚼碎了喂他  像鸟妈妈喂鸟宝宝那样
Chew it up for him, like a mama bird.
-不  琳达  -他可是白金会员
- Linda, no! - He's platinum status!
你疯了么  琳达
You're crazy, Linda!
没关系的  我自己可以
It's all right, guys. I got it.
真是超完美房客
Perfect guest.
也就是说事实是这样的
So let me get this straight.
泰迪撂倒一群傻大个
Teddy beat up a bunch of giant animals.
你把露易丝锁在我们屋里
You locked Louise in our room,
又把客人们锁在各自屋里了
and then you locked the guests in their rooms?
他们想在三点的冰淇淋会餐开始前离开
They were gonna leave before the big ice cream social at 3:00.
琳  先把钥匙给我  好吗
Lin, just give me the key, all right?
-我去把他们放出来  -不给
- I'm gonna let them out. - No.
-快点  -不介
- Yes. - No.
看看你这副德行
Look at yourself.
看看你变成什么样了
Look at what you've turned into!
好吧
Oh, all right.
我只是想办个成功的简易餐馆
All I wanted was a charming bed and breakfast,
别无他求
that's all.
现在这样  我还有什么脸去见上帝
Now what am I gonna say to God when I go to heaven?
我把钥匙弄丢了
I lost the key!
我的天哪  看我都做了些什么
Oh, my God, what have I done?
好了  好了  听着
All right, all right, listen.
你知道的  露易丝是开锁能手
You know Louise picks locks.
可露易丝恨我
Louise hates me.
不  她不恨你  琳
No, she doesn't hate you, Lin.
我敢说她已经从我们房里逃走了
I'm sure she's broken out of our room already.
再会
我去看看泰迪
I'm gonna go deal with Teddy.
你去她房间看看吧
Why don't you try her room?
好吧
Okay.
嗨  宝贝  是妈妈
Hi, honey. It's mommy.
你好  母亲大人
Oh, hello, mother.
请里面坐
Please do come in.
露易丝  抱歉我把你的房间租给了泰迪
Louise, I'm sorry I rented your room to Teddy
还把你锁在我们卧室
and then locked you in our bedroom.
我接受你的道歉  妈妈
I accept your apology, mom.
人非圣贤  孰能无过嘛
Who among us hasn't gone a little overboard from time to time?
谢谢你  宝贝
Aw, thanks, sweetie.
但你还是得向泰迪道歉
And you're gonna apologize to Teddy.
好吧
Okay.
我还要请你帮个忙
And there's something else I need from you.
我刚才还想剪来着
I would just cut it up right now.
不  我不是说这个
Oh. No, not that.
你能帮我把扎维德和塞缪尔夫妇
Will you please help me get Javed
从他们的房间里弄出来吗
and the Samuels out of their rooms?
我把他们锁在了里面
I locked them in
貌似还把钥匙弄丢了
and I... I kind of lost the key.
或许我能帮点忙
There might be something I can do.
扎维德
Javed,
抱歉我把你锁起来了
I'm sorry I locked you in your room.
你想走的话现在可以走了
You're free to go if you wish.
你把我锁起来了吗
You locked me in my room?
-没  -她脑子被门挤了吧
- No. - She's completely bonkers, isn't she?
我说话的时候你们得看着我
Look at me when I'm talking to you!
他们不见了
They're gone.
他们是怎么从上锁的房间逃走的
How did they get out of a locked room?
这是他们最完美的一次逃脱
It was their greatest escape.
看看他们都留下了什么
Look what they left behind.
看  我的舌头被困住了
Look. My tongue is trapped.
它逃了出来
Now it's escaped.
又困住了  又逃了出来
Now it's trapped. Now it's escaped.
快看
Hey, look!
他们还在往下爬呢
They're still climbing down.
你俩还好吧
You two all right?
行李要我帮你拿下去吗
You need any help with your bags?
不用  其实我们是被困在这儿了
No. Uh, actually we're stuck.
拜托帮帮我们
Please help us.
或许可以找个梯子来
I suppose we could get a ladder.
你们觉得我的简易旅馆办得怎么样啊
How much did you like my B&B?
爱死了
A lot.
你们会向朋友推荐吗
Are you gonna recommend us to your friends?
绝对的
Yes!
你们会留下邮箱地址吗
Are you gonna leave me your e-mail address?
必须留
Yes!
给他们送梯子
Get 'em the ladder.
谢谢光临  不好意思了
Uh, thanks for coming. Sorry.
不好意思
Sorry again.
这些算是赔偿
Ah, here's something for your trouble.
两块钱呢  谢谢啊
Two dollars. Thanks a lot.
这种情况下我不知道该给多少小费
I don't know what to tip in this situation.
两块钱也太"大方"了吧
Yeah. Not two dollars.
泰迪  你还好吗
Oh, hey, Teddy. Ah, you all right?
我想我克服了我的恐惧症  鲍勃
I think I worked through my issues, Bob.
我和这只猫头鹰要去喝一杯
Me and the owl are gonna go get a drink.
我敢说里面绝对是个女的
I'm pretty sure there's a woman inside.
他是男的  泰迪
That's a guy, Teddy.
是女的
Oh, that's a woman.
猫头鹰是男的
The owl was a guy.
-是女的  -那只狐狸才是女的
- It's a woman. - The fox was a girl.
狐狸走了吗
Oh. Did the fox leave already?
走了
Yes. Oh.
琳达  你真是一个热情周到的房东
Linda, you are a delightful hostess.
谢谢你  泰迪
Aw, thanks, Teddy!
午餐时见  鲍勃
See you at lunch, Bob.
好了  现在都没事了
Well, that was all right.
也不赖嘛
It was pretty good.
我给我们打B
I give us a B.
B+好了
B plus.
上等简易旅馆
A B&B plus!
我的脸出汗了
My face is sweaty.
吉恩  把那玩意儿拿下来
Gene, take that off.
我才不要呢
Never! Oh!